<npc>
	<name>Estragon</name>
        <file>/peragro/art/3d_art/characters/male01/male01</file>
	<mesh>test</mesh>
	<position sector="World" x="602" y="12.7" z="360"/>
	<race>test</race> <!-- used for stats -->
	<hair><color r="255" g="255" b="255" /></hair>
	<skin><color r="255" g="255" b="255" /></skin>
	<decal><color r="255" g="255" b="255" /></decal>
  
        <aisetting type="stray">
		<value name="base_x">35.0</value>
		<value name="base_y">0.0</value>
		<value name="base_z">106.2</value>
		<value name="radius_x">10.0</value>
		<value name="radius_y">10.0</value>
		<value name="radius_z">10.0</value>
		<value name="interval_base">100</value>
		<value name="interval_rand">50</value>
	</aisetting>

	<inventory>
	</inventory>

	<dialog id="0">
		<function>(if (> (reputation test_dummy) -1) (dialog 01) (dialog 10))</function>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="01">
		<text>Let us not waste our time in idle discourse! Let us do something, while we have the chance!</text>
		<answer href="02">...</answer>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="02">
		<text>It is not every day that we are needed. Not that we personally are needed. Others would meet the case equally well, if not better. To all mankind they were addressed, those cries for help still ringing in our ears!</text>
			<answer href="03">ahh...</answer>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="03">
		<text>But at this place, at this moment of time, all mankind is us, whether we like it or not. Let us make the most of it, before it is too late! Let us represent worthily for once the foul brood to which a cruel fate consigned us! What do you say?</text>
			<answer href="04">I...</answer>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="04">
		<text>It is true that when with folded arms we weigh the pros and cons we are no less a credit to our species. The tiger bounds to the help of his congeners without the least reflection, or else he slinks away into the depths of the thickets.</text>
			<answer href="05">what...</answer>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="05">
		<text>But that is not the question. What are we doing here, that is the question. And we are blessed in this, that we happen to know the answer. Yes, in this immense confusion one thing alone is clear. We are waiting for Godot to come...</text>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="11">
		<text>We are all born mad. Some remain so.</text>
		<answer>Nothing to be done, I suppose.</answer>
		<answer href="12">Was I sleeping, while the others suffered? Am I sleeping now? Tomorrow, when I wake, or think I do, what shall I say of today?</answer>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="12">
		<text>That with Estragon your friend, at this place, until the fall of night, you waited for Godot. That Pozzo passed, with his carrier, and that he spoke to us.</text>
		<answer>Probably. But in all that what truth will there be?</answer>
		<answer href="13">You'll know nothing. You'll tell me about the blows you received and I'll give you an apple...</answer>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="13">
		<text>An apple? You'll give me an apple?</text>
		<answer>I do not have any...</answer>
		<answer href="14">I have one ... Here.</answer>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="14">
		<function>(if (> (inventory count 1) 0) (begin (inventory sub 1) (reputation test_dummy add 1) (dialog 14)) (begin (reputation test_dummy sub 1)(dialog 15)))</function>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="15">
		<text>I remember the maps of the Holy Land. Coloured they were. Very pretty. The Dead Sea was pale blue. The very look of it made me thirsty. That's where we'll go, I used to say, that's where we'll go for our honeymoon. We'll swim. We'll be happy.</text>
		<answer href="11">...</answer>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id="16">
		<text>Nothing to be done.</text>
		<answer>...</answer>
	</dialog>
</npc>
